Rockwell Kent papers 4079547
Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- Series XI: Other Categories
  - Chinaware design:
    - America ware (Vernonware Kilns, Los Angeles): pencil draft (Moby DickÀ) (Box 34)
    - Moby Dick pattern (Vernonware Kilns, Los Angeles): 12 pieces of china (Box 36 & 44)
    - Salamina pattern (Vernonware Kilns, Los Angeles):
      - pencil draft (Box 34)
      - oversize pencil drafts, 2p. (Mapcase 13V-F-06)
      - 6 pieces of china (Box 35)
    - Printed article: "Rockwell Kent and Vernon Kilns." in The Glaze, Vol.6, No.4, p.8 & 9., July 1982 (Box 34)
    - Printed brochure: "Our America, by Rockwell Kent: A New Pattern of Authentic California Vernonware." Los Angeles: Vernon Kilns, À, 4p., 1938 (Box 34)
  - Christmas Cards:
    - 1912-Kathleen and Rockwell Kent: 2 printed copies (Box 37)
    - 1912-Mr. and Mrs. Samuel Loomis Prentiss: ink lettering (Box 37)
    - [ca. 1914]-"Ave Maria;" printed copy (Box 37)
    - 1914-Miss E. Josephine Holgate: printed copy (Box 37)
    - 1914-Kathleen Whiting Kent (Mrs Rockwell): proof copy (Box 37)
    - 1914-Kathleen Whiting Kent (Mrs Rockwell): 4 printed copies (Box 37)
    - 1926-"Christmas!": printed copy (Box 37)
    - 1926-Kimbel, Anthony F.: printed copy (Box 37)
    - 1931-Ashlar Press (August and Maurice Heckscher): printed copy (Box 37)
    - 1931-"Greetings of the season;" printed copy (Box 37)
    - 1935-American Artists Group: prospectus (Box 37)
    - 1935-Kent, Rockwell: printed copy (Box 37)
    - [1936]-"Christmas star;" 2 printed copies (Box 37)
    - 1941-Grenfell Association: ink sketch; pencil drafts, 4p. (Box 37)
    - 1941-"My mirror;" pencil draft (Box 37)
    - 1944-pencil drafts, 2p. proof and ink lettering, 4p. (Box 37)
    - 1949-Sally and Rockwell Kent: printed copy (Box 37)
    - 1953-Sally and Rockwell Kent: printed copy (Box 37)
    - 1954-Sally and Rockwell Kent: printed copy (Box 37)
    - [1955 À]-Sally and Rockwell Kent: printed copy (Box 37)
    - 1958-Sally and Rockwell Kent: printed copy (Box 37)
    - n.d.-Kent, Rockwell and Sally-American Artists Group, NY.:printed copy (Box 37)
    - & n.d.-Spector, Gladys and George: 6 printed cards, 1974; 1976 (Box 37)
    - American Artists Group, N.Y.: 3 printed cards (Box 37)
    - "American Humanist Association;" printed copy (Box 37)
    - [angel]: pencil draft (Box 37)
    - International Workers Order: ink draft; pencil drafts, 3p. (Box 37)
    - [Moby Dick illus., p.13]: printed copy (Box 37)
    - "On earth peace;" printed copy (Box 37)
    - "The trapper;" printed copy (Box 37)
    - Wurrell, Dick:
      - mock-up with ink lettering (Box 37)
      - pencil draft (Box 37)
    - ink drafts, 3p. (Box 37)
    - ink lettering ink sketches, 3p. (Box 37)
    - oversize pencil draft (Mapcase 13V-F-06)
    - pencil drafts, 17p. (Box 37)
    - pencil lettering (Box 37)
    - pencil sketch (black, green and orange) (Box 37)
    - proofs, 6p. (Box 37)
    - Misc. printed cards, 5 cards (Box 37)
    - clipping (Box 37)
    - See also: Advertising: Lentheric: Life Magazine: United Airlines: and Weyerhauser Timber Co.
  - Fabric Design:
    - oversize Deer: sample, mounted on board The Palisades. ca. 1950. tempera, 26 x 28 inches (Lacarda catalog no.58) (Mapcase 13V-F-09)
    - oversize Wheat: sample, mounted on board (Mapcase 13V-F-09)
  - Furniture Design:
    - "Contempora;" pencil sketches, 7p. pencil sketches, 3p. (Box 37)
  - Glass Painting:
    - ink sketch pencil drafts, 20p. (Box 37)
  - Initials and Lettering:
    - American Red Cross scroll:
      - ink lettering text, t.ms., 1p. pencil draft (Box 37)
      - ink and pencil drafts (Box 37)
      - ink drafts, 3p. (Box 37)
      - pencil drafts, 7p. (Box 37)
  - Invitations:
    - "Bennett Cerf [and] Donald Klopfer have the honor to invite you to a so-called tea or inspirational orgy for the spiritual benefit of Rockwell Kent...." [1930 À]. (Box 37)
    - No.1 of an edition limited to 99 copies: printed copy, signed. (Box 37)
    - The Caxton Club (Chicago): see: Exhibitions: The Lakeside Press (Chicago): "The Christening of Moby Dick"
    - Chicago Council of American-Soviet Friendship:
      - "Let there be peace" lecture by Rockwell Kent, 23 printed copy, November 1957 (Box 37)
      - "Let us have peace" lecture by Rockwell Kent, 23 printed copy ", November 1957 (Box 37)
      - Silver jubilee meeting," 15 printed copy, November 1958 (Box 37)
    - Dinner to Dr. Walter E. Traprock F.R.S.S.E.U., 14 September 1921-menu cover: 2 printed copies (Box 37)
    - Goldman, Dr. and Mrs. Leo: Dinner before Rockwell Kent's lecture, 22 printed copy, November 1957 (Box 37)
    - J.C.C.-dinner invitation: see: Advertising-Lentheric, pencil sketches, 9p.
    - Playboy's Fete Futuriste: a cubist costume carnival, 31 printed leaflet, December 1924 (Box 37)
    - Wisconsin Artists Bureau (Milwaukee):
    - "Art is for everyone" lecture by Rockwell Kent: printed announcement & clippings, 5p. (Box 37)
  - Jewelry Design: pencil drafts, 4p. (Box 37)
  - Maps:
    - Greenland and Newfoundland: ink sketch (Box 37)
  - Murals:
    - "American Airlines," pencil sketch on tissue paper, 17 x 14 inches, (study for muralÀ), ca. 1945 (Box 38)
    - The Cape Cinema (Dennis, MA):
      - ink sketch of theater (not in mural) (Box 38)
      - pencil drafts, 4p. (Box 38)
      - oversize pencil drafts, 11p. (Mapcase 13V-F-08)
      - clippings, 2p. (Box 38)
    - General Electric:
      - pencil drafts, 22p. (Box 38)
      - oversize pencil drafts, 7p. (Mapcase 13V-F-08)
      - oversize pencil lettering, 2p. (Mapcase 13V-F-08)
      - pencil lettering and notes, 2p. (Box 38)
      - photographs and blueprints, 18p. (Box 38)
      - watercolor sketch (Box 38)
      - clippings, 2p. (Box 38)
    - Interstate Commerce Commission:
      - pencil draft (Mapcase 13V-F-08)
      - pencil drafts, 2p. (Box 38)
      - oversize watercolor sketches, 2p. (Mapcase 13V-F-08)
      - clipping (Box 38)
    - Post Office Department ("Puerto Rican Mural"):
      - pencil drafts, 6p. (Box 38)
      - oversize pencil sketch (Mapcase 13V-F-08)
      - photostat of sketch clippings, 13p. (Box 38)
      - pencil drafts, 3p. (Box 38)
  - Record jacket (includes labels and phonodiscs):
    - Asgaard Records:
    - "A Christmas Story" with printed and hand-lettered label: phonodisc, 10 in. Story read by Sally Kent. (Box 38)
    - Vanguard records:
      - oversize ink sketch (Mapcase 13V-F-06)
      - The Three Ravens: Songs of Folk and Minstrelsy our of Elizabethan England. Record jacket only. (Mapcase 13V-F-06)
      - ink tracing (Box 38)
      - pencil drafts, 2p. (Box 38)
      - pencil sketch (Box 38)
      - oversize 18 proofs in various states (Mapcase 13V-F-06)
  - Silverware Design:
    - drafts and sketches, 39p. (Box 38)
  - Stamps:
    - Christmas seals-1939:
      - pencil draft (Box 38)
      - pencil sketch (Box 38)
      - printed copies (blue and red), 100 stamps on 1 perforated sheet, 2 copies (Box 38)
      - printed copies (blue and red), 72 stamps in 6 envelopes (Box 38)
      - clipping (Box 38)
    - "On earth peace":
      - printed copies (blue and red), 4 stamps on one perforated sheet (Box 38)
      - printed copies (blue and red), 42 stamps on one perforated sheet (Box 38)
    - "United with Russia for Victory;" pencil drafts, 3p. (Box 38)
    - Workers' Defense League-Arkansas Centennial:
      - pencil drafts, 5p. (Box 38)
      - printed copies: 2 perforated sheets and 1 mounted p. (Box 38)
    - clipping (Box 38)
    - see also: Magazine illustration: Art in America.
  - Stationery:
    - Abbott, Katharine Tiffany (Mrs. Gordon)-mailing label: printed copy (Box 38)
    - Briarcombe Farm (Winona, MN): embossed device (Box 38)
    - Chicago Latin School: note paper and envelope, 1927. 2 copies (Box 38)
    - Cowdin, John Cheever:
      - place cards: pencil drafts, 2p. (Box 38)
      - printed copies, 6p. (lettered by Juliet Koenig Smith) (Box 38)
      - invitation, 2 items (Box 38)
    - Jones, Dan Burne: letterhead and envelope (Box 38)
    - Jones, Jacqui (Mrs. Dan Burne): letterhead and envelope (Box 38)
    - Kent, Clara: pencil sketch (Box 38)
    - Kent, Frances Lee (Mrs. Rockwell): bank check with Rockwell Kent's emblem, printed copy (Box 38)
    - Kent, Rockwell:
      - letterhead (printed copy): (Box 38)
      - torn sheet (Box 38)
      - mailing label, printed copy (Box 38)
      - mailing label and note to postmaster (Box 38)
      - mailing label and sticker (Box 38)
      - receipt from the Pynson Printers, 18, February1928 (Box 38)
      - woodcut monogram, 4 envelopes (large and small) (Box 38)
    - Rockwell Kent Incorporated (Egypt, Arlington, VT.): letterheads, 2p. (Box 38)
    - The Wayfarers Travel Agency: letterhead (Box 38)
    - Unidentified letterhead: printed copy (Box 38)
  - Tile Designs:
    - "Militis in Galea nidum fecere columbiae;" pencil drafts, 3p. (Box 38)
    - "Pax vobiscum;" pencil sketches, 2p. (Box 38)
    - Swans: pencil drafts, 4p. (Box 38)
    - ink and pencil draft (Box 38)
    - ink and watercolor draft (Box 38)
    - pencil drafts, 8p. (Box 38)
    - watercolor and pencil drafts, 3p. (Box 38)
    - watercolor sketches, 6p. (Box 38)
  - Tile Stencils:
    - "Militis in Galea nidum fecere columbiae;" stencil pieces with pencil drafts, 13p. (Box 38)
    - pencil draft (Box 38)
  - Tombstones:
    - ink and pencil draft (Box 38)
    - pencil drafts, 7p. (Box 38)
  - Wall Decoration:
    - watercolor drafts, 3p. (Box 38)
  - Wrapping Paper:
    - oversize silver design printed on black, 2p. (Box 38)
- Series XII: Miscellaneous Drafts and Sketches-Early Work
  - animals:
    - ink pencil, 7p. (Box 39)
    - oversize pencil, 2p. (Mapcase 13V-F-10)
  - boat:
    - watercolor and pencil (Box 39)
  - faces:
    - ink, 7p. ink and pencil, 4p. pencil, 12p. (Box 39)
  - figures:
    - ink, 56p. and 2p. (Box 39)
    - ink and pencil, 11p. (Box 39)
    - oversize ink and pencil (Mapcase 13V-F-10)
    - ink tracings, 2p. (Box 39)
    - pencil, 84p. (Box 39)
    - oversize pencil (Mapcase 13V-F-10)
  - figures (medieval):
    - ink, 2p. (Box 39)
    - ink and pencil (Box 39)
    - watercolor (Box 39)
    - watercolor and pencil (Box 39)
  - flying figures:
    - ink and pencil (Box 39)
    - pencil, 8p. (Box 39)
  - landscape:
    - ink, 5p. (Box 39)
    - pencil, 35p. (Box 39)
    - oversize pencil (Mapcase 13V-F-10)
  - stage: watercolor (Box 39)
  - unsorted:
    - ink, 12p. (Box 39)
    - ink and pencil, 5p. (Box 39)
    - pencil, 44p. (Box 39)
- Series XIII: Miscellaneous Drafts and Sketches
  - oversize airplane: watercolor (Mapcase 13V-F-10)
  - angels: pencil, 11p. and 1p. (Box 40)
  - animals:
    - ink (Mapcase 13V-F-10)
    - ink and pencil, 3p. (Box 40)
    - pencil, 16p. (Box 40)
    - oversize pencil, 2p. (Mapcase 13V-F-10)
  - birds: ink sketch and pencil sketch (Box 40)
  - boats:
    - brown crayon (Box 40)
    - ink (Box 40)
    - ink and pencil, 4p. and 1p. (Box 40)
    - oversize ink and pencil (Mapcase 13V-F-10)
    - pencil, 12p. and 2p. (Box 40)
    - oversize pencil, 2p. (Mapcase 13V-F-10)
  - books:
    - ink, 3p. (Box 40)
    - ink and pencil, 3p. (Box 40)
    - pencil, 7p. (Box 40)
    - oversize pencil (Mapcase 13V-F-10)
  - children:
    - charcoal (Mapcase 13V-F-10)
    - ink and pencil, 3p. (Box 40)
    - pencil, 16p. and 1p. (Box 40)
  - equestrian figures:
    - pencil, 3p. (Box 40)
  - faces:
    - ink, 2p. (Box 40)
    - ink and pencil (Box 40)
    - pencil, 37p. (Box 40)
    - oversize pencil, 3p. (Mapcase 13V-F-10)
  - figures:
    - oversize charcoal, 9p. (Mapcase 13V-F-10)
    - oversize charcoal and ink crayon (Mapcase 13V-F-10)
    - ink, 8p. and 3p. (Box 40)
    - oversize ink, 3p. (Mapcase 13V-F-10)
    - ink and pencil, 13p. (Box 40)
    - ink tracing (Box 40)
    - lithographic crayon (Box 40)
    - pencil, 199p. and 5p. (Box 40-41)
    - oversize pencil, 4p. (Mapcase 13V-F-10)
  - figures (aviators): ink and pencil pencil (Box 41)
  - figures (climbing): pencil, 15p. (Box 41)
  - figure (medieval): watercolor and pencil (Box 41)
  - oversize figures (mother and child): pencil (Mapcase 13V-F-10)
  - figure (mythological): pencil, 2p. (Box 41)
  - figure (skier): pencil (Box 41)
  - hands:
    - pencil, 26p. (Box 41)
    - oversize pencil, 2p. (Mapcase 13V-F-10)
  - landscape:
    - ink (Box 41)
    - oversize pastel and pencil (Mapcase 13V-F-10)
    - pencil, 23p. and 2p. (Box 41)
    - watercolor (Box 41)
    - watercolor, 2p. (Box 41)
  - lily: pencil (Box 41)
  - ocean: ink (Box 41)
  - set of illus.:
    - pencil, 10p. (Box 41)
    - pencil, 10p. (Box 41)
  - statue:
    - ink and pencil (Box 41)
    - pencil (Box 41)
  - swords: ink (Box 41)
  - watch: pencil (Box 41)
  - unsorted:
    - ink, 14p. and 1p. (Box 42)
    - ink and pencil, 3p. (Box 41)
    - ink (red and black) (Box 42)
    - pencil, 53p. (Box 42)
    - oversize pencil, 2p. (Mapcase 13V-F-10)
    - watercolor, 3p. (Box 41)
  - misc. scraps, etc.: 62p. and 1p. (Box 42)
    - oversize 1p. (Mapcase 13V-F-10)
- Series XIV: Articles, Broadside, Clippings, Obituaries,and Photographs
  - Articles and clippings:
    - Rockwell Kent, 1882-1971. A Biographical Dictionary of Architects in Maine. Vol.IV, No.4, 1987. Published by the Maine Historic Preservation Commission. (Box 43)
    - Miscellaneous articles and clippings (Box 43)
  - Broadside:
    - "Farewell, Great Friend," obituary poem by Dan Burne Jones. (Box 43)
  - Clippings, 81 p. (Box 43)
  - Ephemera:(unclassified items) (Box 43)
  - Notes on the Herman and Aveve Cohen gift., 1986 (Box 43)
  - Obituaries of Kent (Box 43)
  - Peace movement: clippings and misc., 33p. (Box 43)
  - Photographs, 8 items (Box 43)
  - Programs (Box 43)
- Series XV: Additions to the Collection
  This series contains material which was asscessioned after the main collection was processed.
  - Correspondence:
    - Kent, Rockwell. Correspondence with Dale Nichols. 1953-1971, 25 t.l.s. in 1 ringed binder. (Box 45, Folder 1)
    - Kent, Rockwell. To Robert Poehler, 2 t.l.s., 1968 and 1969 (Box 45, Folder 2)
    - Kent, Rockwell. To "Arthur", 1 t.l.s., 25 November 1948 (Box 45, Folder 3)
    - Kent, Rockwell. To Robert S. Poehler, t.l.s., 1 page, December 27, 1968 (Box 45, Folder 4)
    - Kent, Rockwell. To Thomas Maloney, 2 t.l.s., 6 February and 13 March 1956 (Box 45, Folder 5)
    - Kent, Rockwell. To Thomas Brendel Brumbaugh, 2 t.l.s., 2 June 1966 and 30 August 1967 (Box 45, Folder 5)
    - Kent, Rockwell. To Arthur Price, 29 April 1942 (Box 45, Folder 6)
    - Kent, Rockwell. To Arthur Price at Sears, Roebuck and Co. in Chicago, 6 t.l.s., 4 April 1942-16 December 1947 (Box 45, Folder 7)
    - Kent, Rockwell to "Walter", 1950 January 1 (Box 45, Folder 10)
    - Kent, Rockwell to Goodman, M.Y., 1961 April 5 (Box 45, Folder 11)
    - Kent, Rockwell to Cutcliffe, Mr., 1962 October 15 (Box 45, Folder 12)
    - Kent, Rockwell to Thomajan, Puzant Kevork, 1970 June 18 (Box 45, Folder 13)
    - Typed letter signed To E.R. Brown at the Branden Press in Bostonone, Ausable Forks, New York, 30 June 1965. (Box 46, Folder 1)
      On letterhead featuring his personal red tree woodcut design, concerning illustrative work: ". .. the manuscript of Mr. Abbe's book ... is being read aloud to me --and to herself --by my wife. We are thrilled by what we have read so far, but I must beg your indulgence of us for the time such reading will necessitate. I will write to Mr. Abbe when we shall have read far enough in it for me to know whether I have drawings that might serve to illustrate it." Kent did indeed furnish illustrations for George Abbe's The Non-Cottformist: The Autobiography ifa Lonscience, which was issued by the Branden Press in 1966.
    - Typed letter signed To Arthur Price, 29 April 1942 (Box 46, Folder 2)
      On Kent's personal letterhead (incorporating a small design of a tree, printed in red) of Ausable Forks, New York. In the advertising department at Sears, Roebuck and Co. in Chicago, reporting: "Inspiration takes time, or, rather, leisure; and I have been so overwhelmed by commissions that demand little inspiration, but that may furnish the means for that needed leisure, that I haven't been able to give Sears, Roebuck's cover problem more than a comer in the back of my mind. I can blame it all on our war effort. Apparently, the only way an artist can serve his country now is by doing something else. My 'something else' is milk production .... To enlarge my bam I have had to accept every job that came along.. .. Do you remember my speaking to you about a collection of Kentiana that was consigned to me.. .. One box must weigh 150 or 200 lbs. And there's a smaller package. They are here unopened. If you'll come and see me some time, we'll open them together and have a good time about it. ..."
    - Typed letter signed To Walter E. Koons, 27 January 1933 (Box 46, Folder 3)
      On letterhead decorated with his personalized red tree woodcut design, Ausable Forks, New York. Replying in full: "I am sending you my definition of music, although on seeing Mrs. Franklin Roosevelt's name in your list I was almost inclined to throw your letter in the waste-basket. It is of course understood that you will print my little contribution in full or not at all"
    - Typed letters (5) signed ("Affectionately, Rockwell"), 5 February 1959 through 6 February 1961 (Box 46, Folder 4)
      On letterhead featuring his personal red tree woodcut design, Ausable Forks, with three typed envelopes (one featuring his "on Earth Peace" dove stamp; addressed variously: Mrs. Marion William Edgerton, Mrs. Marian Rigg Edgerton and Mrs. H. C. Foley; one torn open; usual postmarks; minor wear). Mostly relating to his travels in the Soviet Union, touching briefly upon artistic, political, personal and social endeavors: "[14 July 1959] ... In a few days we go abroad again --this time first to Vienna, where, along with, 1 must admit, such distinguished Russians as Ulanova, Shostakovich, Oistakh, Gilels and maybe others, and a number of worth-while men and women of other nationalities (I will be the only American) I am to serve on the Fine Arts jury of the great Youth Festival. The Festival will be attended by talented delegations of Youth from virtually every country in the world --even, and despite the displeasure of our State Department, America.. .. It happens that in Rumania, at a certain institution there, they have discovered the nearest thing to a Fountain Of Youth. I think of going there to quaff it. And if I do, look outL ..."; "[12 Jan. 1960] ... I am delighted that you want some peace seals.. .. It is a hopeful year for peace, and you had better be on the alert to shut your eyes and ears to the Russian arts, for we are going to see more and more of them in this country. Maybe they will help drive our Micky Spi11anes under cover --and I don't mean book covers.. .. It has been far too cold for me to try my wings, because if I am to model myself on the classic cupids I would of course have to fly around naked. But I guess the cupids, or angels, are hidden from mortal eyes. At least I haven't seen any yet. ..." "[14 March 1960] .... [W]e have just been invited by the Ambassador to attend the gala opening of the Georgian Dancers at the Metropolitan Opera House this coming Sunday .... [W]e made another trip to New York, this one two weeks ago.. .. I had to chair a luncheon affair, and because of the overflow subscription to it, a dinner right upon its heels. Going through the same performance twice on the same day is thoroughly nauseating ...."; and "[6 Feb. 1961] ... [W]e had a wonderful time in the Soviet Union and ... we have had a hell of a time ever since trying not only to catch up with the accumulation of mail that awaited us but keep pace with the deluge of fan mail from Russia that keeps pouring in. This prophet is certainly not without honor somewhere.. .. [I]f I am too late now to wish you a happy New Year, I can at least wish you a happy ten months and twenty-three days of this hopeful year of 1961 --hopeful in that we haven't Nixon as President...."
    - Memorandum, signed with initials svj, To Mr. Seagrave re. Rockwell Kent cuts, 6 February 1931. 1 page. (Box 46, Folder 5)
      Discussing the Kent cuts, and a large manila envelope from the Morton Sundour Co. Inc. [noted for interior design} addressed to Cleveland Randall at the Strauss Bldg. [The New Straus Building Fifth Avenue at Forty Sixth Street, New York City. It was built by S.W. Straus the leading mortgage bond brokerage firm in New York City.]
      The letter also states Doremus paid Kent and Lankes a total of $4.040.00.
  - Manuscripts:
    - "What is Music?". Typed manuscript, comprising 16 lines, which he has signed at the bottom (Box 46, Folder 3)
      "Man is a product of experience, a living organism, finely adapted to the conditions of life, and attuned to the prevailing order of the universe as his senses apprehend it. Aesthetics are inherent to that order; they are its coraliary. With faculties minutely sensitive to these prevailing laws man uses them to re-create more poignantly - more humanely, at least - a portion of his universe; he gives expression, form, to mental imagery. And that, achieved - in painting, sculpture, music, writing and the rest - is Art."
      During the 1930s, Walter E. Koons was Music Supervisor for the National Broadcasting Company, New York. In preparation for a book he was writing, Koons wrote to many (over 170) notable figures (Einstein, Shaw, Aldous Huxley, etc.) asking them "Will you please give me your definition of music --not just your appreciation of music-making nor your reactions to it, but whal musk(in the abstract) means you.
  - Documents:
    - Publisher's contract for "It's Me O Lord" December 9, 1953, signed by Kent; plus unsigned contact; plus 2 invoices. (Box 45, Folder 4)
  - Art:
    - Lankes, J.J. 19 of the 28 Drawings by Kent cut in wood. All were made for the Doremus advertising agency in New York, founded in 1903. (Box 46, Folder 5)
      The numbers of the plates in the Dan Burne Jones bibliography are: 602,605,618,596,598,595,615,616,603,669,695,694,697,611, 612,671,639,610,606.
  - Photographs:
    - Folder of mounted photographs of Kent (Box 45, Folder 8)
  - Printed:
    - 2 brochures (Box 45, Folder 9)